
{"type":"cloze","front":"A right triangle has three sides and a __________ degree angle.","back":"A right triangle has three sides and a 90 degree angle.","blank":"90"}
{"type":"qa","front":"Is there a Nobel Prize in Math?","back":"No"}
{"type":"cloze","front":"There is no __________ in Mathematics.","back":"There is no Nobel Prize in Mathematics.","blank":"Nobel Prize"}
{"type":"qa","front":"sasdf","back":"asdf"}
{"type":"qa","front":"using functions is good right? ","back":"of course!"}
{"type":"cloze","front":"We should always use __________.","back":"We should always use functions.","blank":"functions"}
{"type":"cloze","front":"this is the __________ statement","back":"this is the full statement","blank":"full"}
{"type":"qa","front":"this is the front","back":"this is now the back"}
{"type":"qa","front":"This is the question, isn't it?","back":"This is the answer for sure!"}
{"type":"qa","front":"is this the front?","back":"Yup!"}
{"type":"qa","front":"how about this?","back":"nope!"}
{"type":"qa","front":"trying the front again","back":"and now the back"}
{"type":"qa","front":"on the front","back":"on the back"}
{"type":"qa","front":"now is the front","back":"now back"}
{"type":"qa","front":"front stuff","back":"back stuff"}
{"type":"qa","front":"this i the front","back":"this is the back"}
{"type":"qa","front":"now this is the question 350","back":"and this is the asnwer"}
{"type":"qa","front":"queestion on 351","back":"answer now"}
{"type":"qa","front":"question at 353","back":"answer at 353"}
{"type":"qa","front":"this is the question 356","back":"answer"}
{"type":"qa","front":"question 428","back":"answer 428"}
{"type":"qa","front":"front 429","back":"back 429"}
